## Sukhrob Ilyosbekov

Age: 22

Nationality: Uzbekistan Residence: Malaysia Experience: 3+ years

Email address: <a href="mailto:suxrobGM@gmail.com">suxrobGM@gmail.com</a>

Web: <a href="https://suxrobgm.net">https://suxrobgm.net</a>

Facebook: <a href="https://facebook.com/suxrobgm">https://facebook.com/suxrobgm</a>
LinkedIn: <a href="https://linkedin.com/in/suxrobgm">https://linkedin.com/in/suxrobgm</a>
GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/suxrobGM">https://github.com/suxrobGM</a>



## **Profile**

Thinking "out of the box" to provide software-based solutions.

.NET Developer having over 3 years of extensive experience in complete software development life cycle (SDLC) involving Requirements Gathering, Analysis, Design, Development, Testing, Packaging, Deploying and Supporting of Windows Applications, Web Applications and Mobile Applications on Microsoft platform, and Game development on the Unity platform. Experience in Agile Methodology for full life-cycle of the project.

#### Software skills include:

- Languages: C#, Python, C/C++, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, F#, HTML, CSS, SQL
- Databases: MS SQL, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, MS Access
- Software: Visual Studio, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio Code, DotPeek, Unity 3D, Git
- Technology Stack: ASP.NET Core, WPF, WinForms, Xamarin.Forms, .NET Core, Blazor Web Assembly, Unity 3D, ReactJS, Django, Bootstrap, jQuery, AJAX, RESTful API, SignalR

## Work experience

### Pentalight Technology • Malaysia

#### **Software Developer**

03/2020 - present

- Developed the multiplayer functionality for the smart city project in Unity platform.
- Integrated user interface (UI) and various HUD for VR platform.
- Integrated Photon Unity Networking.
- Integrated SteamVR.

#### Freelancer.com

#### **Freelance Software Developer**

02/2019 - 02/2020

- Designed and developed various application in ASP.NET, WPF and Xamarin.Forms.
- Designed and developed various API and wrapper libraries in .NET
- Developed natural language processing applications using Python NLP libraries.
- Designed and maintained front-end for web and mobile applications.
- Wrote unit tests to improve code predictability and documentation.
- Developed supporting tools to reduce development time.
- Used coding methods in specific programming languages to initiate and improve program execution and functionality.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.

#### EC Dev Team • Uzbekistan

#### **Game Developer**

07/2016 – 01/2019

- Developed RTS game in Clausewitz Engine which called "Hearts of Iron: Economic Crisis"
- Managed team of enthusiastic developers.
- Designed and developed game artificial intelligence (AI) logics.
- Programmed hardcore game mechanics.
- Scripted world map of the game.
- Developed various software tools for developers.
- Balanced game difficulty and technology trees.

## **Education**

# INTI International College Subang Subang Jaya • Malaysia

08/2019 - present

- American Degree Transfer Program
- Major: Computer Science

## Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand • Uzbekistan

09/2017 - 06/2019

- Bachelor of Science
- Major: Software Engineering

### **Awards**

#### Top-10 team

Tashkent University of Information Technologies 02/2018

• Top-10 team in the contest between IT Universities in Uzbekistan.

### First place

Tashkent University of Information Technologies

12/2017

• Winner in the individual ACM ICPC contest between TUIT students.

## **Strengths**

Ability to learn from mistakes • Creative thinking • Confident • Critical thinking

Working quickly - Accuracy - Solving complex problems

## **Skills**

## **Programming Languages**

C#

C/C++

Python

JavaScript **TREE** 

TypeScript ■■■■

Java ■■■■■

PHP ■■□□□

HTML/CSS ■■■■■

SQL **IIII** 

**F**# ■■■□□

## Frameworks & Technologies

.NET ■■■■

ASP.NET ■■■■■

WPF ■■■■■

Xamarin.Forms

ReactJS ■■■□□

Qt ■■□□

Unity 3D ■■■■

ML.NET

Entity Framework

Unit Testing ■■■□

Bootstrap 4

Git ■■■■

ADO.NET ■■■□

jQuery ■■■■